hamidashita kaze wo atsumete mitai na
I want to try and gather the unrestrained winds
nami no saki tsutatte kanata e kaketeku
I'll run toward the horizon alongside the wave crests
kakugo wa kimatteru
I've made my decision
michi wa tookutemo
even if there's a long way to go on that road
egaita mirai e tsudzuiteru
I'll continue towards the future I've planned
toki ga bokura wo sekashite kodou ga supiido agetetta
time rushes us, the heartbeat speeds up
yume no naka de mezametemo onaji hikari wo sagashita
when I woke in the middle of a dream, I kept searching for that same light
kagayaku hoshizora no shita kazoekirenai seiza to kage
under the shining star-lit sky, with countless constellations and shadows
sono saki ni kimi wa nani wo nani wo mitsumete iru darou
there was something beyond that, what were you gazing at?
nani wo mitsumete iru darou
what were you gazing at?
Mess up... the village, you say?!
I won't let you do that
no matter what!
I mean, there's no way
just the four of you can do that!
But, we can...
A person who knows village matters
very well gave us information
on where and how to attack.
Knows village matters very well...
It couldn't be!
You mean Orochimaru?!
Who knows...?
Well, that's how it is,
so we can't have you guys living.
Can you see this?
Paper Bombs!
We're going to detonate
the Paper Bombs
after we've left here...
There's nowhere to run...
There's no chance of someone
coming to save you.
Prepare yourselves.
It's better than going back
to the Academy, isn't it?
Rest in peace.
Hey! Just a minute!
Farewell, real me.
Dash, Wonder, Zigzag Run!
Chased, Chased
and Mistaken
It should've just been
hunting for treasure,
but to think this would happen...
Sure enough, nothing good comes
of being together with you
on missions, Naruto!
This isn't the time to be saying that!
They're attempting to mess up
the Leaf Village by impersonating us!
Then how're we going
to get out of here?!
Well...
If I use the Rasengan,
I could somehow...
They'd notice that!
It'd be the end if we were
to get ambushed outside.
Then, with your Fang Over Fang...
That'd be the same, the same!
You moron!
Then what should we do?!
If I use
my Protective 8 Trigrams 64 Palms...
I get it!
With that we can weather this crisis
without the guys outside noticing!
If I could just loosen
these ropes a little...
Leave that to me!
Naruto?!
All right!
Me, too!
Kiba...
Akamaru...
Just a little more...
It snapped...
Protective 8 Trigrams...
64 Palms!
Now then,
shall we go as arranged?
— Kiba!
— Yeah!
— Hinata!
— Yes!
Naruto!
I know!
Hinata!
You okay?
What...?
Hey, Hinata!
Cut our ropes before you faint.
Right.
It seems the guys outside
are gone.
It doesn't look like this place
is going to hold up now.
It'd be best for us
to escape as soon as we can.
What's that?!
It's the buried treasure chest.
Leave it be!
It's a fake anyway.
And there might be
some kind of trap set.
But it's our mission to
take this back with us, so...
There really might be
buried treasure in it, right?!
Byakugan!
It looks empty inside...
Wait, there's paper inside.
Isn't it a Paper Bomb?
It doesn't seem to be
anything dangerous...
Then I guess I'll take it for now.
Come on, there's no need
to go to the trouble of...
But it might make for a good mark
to distinguish him from the imposter...
I get it.
Akamaru, you're the mark for
the real me, so stay close to me.
There's no time.
I'll be going with our Fang Over Fang.
Make sure you keep up!
Right.
Man-Beast Clone...
Fang Over Fang!
You okay, Hinata?
I'm fine... I just have to follow
after Kiba, so... I'll be o...
Hinata!
All right!
You okay, Hinata?
Naruto!
Does your leg hurt?
Kiba...
If your leg hurts, say so first.
I was thinking
I must not cause trouble, so...
Actually, that is trouble.
I'm sorry...
Surprisingly, this might be
the weakness of our team.
Hinata shows too much
concern for us.
Naruto and I speak too bluntly
to each other and we get into fights...
Now that you mention it...
If we'd take on our missions while being
a little conscious of stuff like that,
we might...
become a pretty good team.
Got it!
I'll try...
All right. Then Naruto and I will go
after those guys.
Hinata, you come later.
Your leg's hurt, so don't force things...
Got it.
Listen up. You're hurt, Hinata.
So you follow later.
I just said that, didn't I?
Did you?
Right... Thanks...
Let's go, Naruto!
I have to hurry, too...
I'm back!
You're back, Naruto?
We couldn't catch up
with them, huh...?
Naruto? Kiba?!
Was I here just now?!
Yeah.
That one was an imposter!
Say what?!
But the dog didn't notice anything...
He can't be sniffed out even
with the nose of a Ninja Hound!
Akamaru was fooled, too!
We've got trouble!
To the Hokage, immediately.
Right!
Akamaru! You remember the smell
of that Agari old man, right?!
After him!
Tsunade-sama!
We've just received
a communication...!
Nobody realizes it.
Stay sharp.
Our mission isn't over yet, so...
That's right.
The crucial part comes now.
Someone's coming!
We found you, imposters!
We'll kick your butts!
So, you're alive...
Naturally!
This time it's your turn
to prepare yourselves...
After all, this is our home field.
There are times when you lose
even when fighting
on your home field!
We won't let you get away!
Hinata?!
I'm going to inform the Hokage!
Naruto, you go after the imposters!
Got... it.
Hey...
Upon careful thought,
the real Hinata hasn't come yet...!
You imposter!
What the...?!
What're you doing to Hinata?!
It's just like I'm the imposter.
Naruto!
What're you doing?!
Well...
He's an imposter!
What?!
Prepare yourself, imposter!
Hey! Wait a minute...!
Hey, you're also an imposter!
Even if you can copy
the appearance and scent,
you can't go so far as
copy Ninjutsu, right?!
Let's go, Akamaru.
Fang Over...?
Knocked out...?
No way. It was just a punch,
and I didn't even use a Jutsu...
Come to think of it...
I was slugged good and hard,
but I didn't feel it at all.
Hey! Weren't you going
to mess up the village?!
You guys are utterly weak!
Damn it!
I'll catch the fake Hinata,
so you handle yourself somehow!
Leave me to me!
Hold it!
I wonder if I got overly ambitious
and borrowed too many books...
Hey, Naruto!
You...
You moron!
Your butt is so heavy
you fell right on it!
Ugly! Ugly!
Forehead girl!
I'll kick your butt
the next time I see you!
I'll kick your butt,
no matter what!
Sakura, get out of the way!
Naruto.
I'll kick your butt!
Why?!
What?
Why's the Naruto who ran that way
coming from over here?
I'm off on a delivery.
Right. Take care.
What is it?! You okay, Ayame?!
Yeah. Naruto suddenly flew in...
What...?
Na-ru-to!
How dare you do that
to my daughter...?!
What...?
I'm okay, Dad.
No, you rest a bit.
I will have Naruto take the responsibility
and make the delivery!
What?!
But, but I...
If you refuse,
I'll never let you eat
my ramen ever again!
This isn't the time for me
to be making a delivery!
I finished the delivery!
Okay! Good work!
Where did he go?!
My... imposter!
This jerk was also weak...
Kiba... Stop... Forgive me...
That might've worked on Naruto.
But I hate soppy stuff...
like that!
Did these guys seriously
intend to attack the village...?
Where are you, imposter?!
Come out!
Hey!
Could it be that I came here?
Yeah, you did.
You'll be paying me
for what you ate earlier.
That jerk...!
Forty-five plates...
Here.
Eating and running with
someone else's face...
That imposter...
He's not messing up the village,
he's messing up my reputation.
Hey...
No way...!
My Golden Delicious Ninja Way
Ramen Pure Heart of Fire
I'd been setting aside!
I won't allow it...!
No matter what, I won't allow it...!
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
— Go!
— Where is he?!
— Where's the imposter?!
— Where are you?!
— Imposter!
Where are you?! Come out!
I'll kill you, imposter!
I'll pay the bill later!
— Find him!
— Where is he?!
There he is!
Hey!
— I won't let you get away!
— Got you!
— I've got you!
— You're wrong!
— Is it you?!
— I'm not an imposter!
Calm down, guys!
The imposter isn't carrying
a chest on his back!
— What?
— It's not him?
— Now that you mention it...
— That's right.
That's right!
Then...
It's him!
Yikes!
At the end of the day,
these guys were nothing special.
Hey, are these guys really
Orochimaru's henchmen?
Who knows?
The Hokage will look
into the details for us.
That's right.
Man, I'm tired.
My shoulders got stiff from carrying
this thing around the whole time.
Naruto! Kiba!
Oh, the real Hinata's come back.
Hey, Hinata! Over here!
Naruto!
He's not carrying the chest on his back...
Then this Naruto...
He's the imposter!
Gentle Fist!
Oh, boy. I feel bad for that Naruto...
— What?!
A test?!
This mission was a test
in order to see the teamwork
of you three.
A Shinobi will often have to
form teams with various others
in response to the qualities
and conditions of the mission.
At such times,
failing if teamed with
a certain other person is a problem.
And so I gave you a mission
that was easy at the start.
And I made it so along
the way...
something would happen
involving a village crisis.
At that time,
I wanted to see whether
you could handle it as a team.
So that's what it was...
That's harsh!
We would've died if
we'd made the slightest mistake.
It's okay. I got the story about
you guys from Tsunade-sama.
It was set up so even if
you were to make a mistake,
you would only be injured.
Since this time around
you had the Ninja Hound-dog Akamaru,
I enlisted the help
of the Kedouin Clan...
so you wouldn't be able
to distinguish the enemy.
And?
How did these three do?
Let me see...
They floundered part of the way
and I was worried about the outcome...
But I shall pass them.
In terms of results,
they did capture us, so...
Oh, yeah.
That's...!
It was more or less
our mission to bring this, so.
With this, our mission is complete.
There's no point in going
to the trouble of bringing...
No, no.
There is something important inside
that I must give to you, Hokage-sama.
Farewell, Naruto. Take it easy.
You, too.
— See ya.
— Yeah.
Are they going to look
like that forever?
It seems they'll get their own faces back
naturally in a few days.
I see...
What's this...?!
"INVOICE RE: NINJA PROFICIENCY TEST FOR
NARUTO UZUMAKI, KIBA INUZUKA, HINATA HYUGA"
A bill for the recent training...?!
Here... he said he'd be glad
to cooperate...
It comes to this much?
This is a hard world to live in,
isn't it?
My name is Tsunade...
My concern now is a debt
that absolutely will not go down.
More like, it's growing, isn't it?
I shouldn't have become...
the likes of Hokage...!
kaze ga fuite aa
the wind blows
itai kienai omoi
the pain, the memories won't disappear
nani wo motte ikou ka
what should be brought along?
atsumete hitotsu
assemble them into a piece
nido to nai nido to nai
there is no second chance, never
suteru nante baka mitai
how foolish it is to throw away
mujaki ni natte aa
acting so innocently
imeeji
the images
kitto sore wa owaranai
it probably will not end
ai no mune kogase
burn that love-filled heart
sen no yume watare
sail across a thousand dreams
juuoumujin kakete
running freely
te ni tsukamu sekai
to take hold of the world in hand
kumo ga chigirete
the clouds scatter
hi ga mata ochite
the sun sets yet again
hitori no pareedo ga ugokidasu
the solo parade begins to move
bouken kichijitsu shinpaku joushou
adventure, lucky day, geart beat, rising
meian souguu seimei souai
decisive, encounter, life, mutual love
No, it's gone, gone, gone!
Where'd you put it, Naruto?
Oh, if you mean that, I wrote it.
You wrote it?
And I gave it to
a Delivery Ninja.
You gave it?
So it should reach
the other party today.
You idiot!
At this rate, my life as a writer will...
More importantly,
let's get the training started.
Shut up and come with me, Naruto!
We have to get that back at any cost!
Next time:
"Oh?! Please ♥ Mister Postman."